这个故事开始于2004年9月22日
This story begins on September 22nd, 2004,
地点是澳大利亚的悉尼
in Sydney, Australia,
当时324名旅客登上了一架
when 324 people boarded a plane
飞往洛杉矶的飞机
to Los Angeles.
别关门
Hold the door!
就像当天所有的航班一样
Like any flight that day,
这次航班也是由陌生人组成
this was comprised of strangers...
在他们当中  有一位医生
among them, a doctor
一个逃犯
and a fugitive,
一名士兵
a soldier
一个摇滚歌星
and a rock star,
一个骗子
a con man
乐透彩票赢家
and a lottery winner
闹不合的夫妇
and an estranged couple,
未来的单身母亲
a single mother-to-be...
和一个失去信仰的人
And a man whose faith was lost.
就在大洋815航班在海洋上飞行的时候
As Oceanic flight 815 flew high over the ocean...
这一群素昧平生的人...
this group of strangers...
这很正常
It's normal.
他们的命运即将联系在一起
Was about to be joined together.
别担心
Don't worry.
在一个神秘的岛上
on a mysterious Island...
这地方与别处不同
This place is different.
远离家乡...
Far from home...
飞行员说我们偏离航道几千英里
The pilot said we were over a thousand miles off course.
他们发现自己踏上了一段旅程
They found themselves on a journey...
这是个奇迹发生的地方
It's a place where miracles happen.
快跑
Run!
他们从未想过的旅程
They could never have imagined.
不是只有我们在岛上
We're not alone.
他们彼此相爱...
They loved...
是的  我爱他
Yes, I love him!
却只能分开
And lost
查里
Charlie!
他们勇敢抗争
They fought...
这是我们的岛
This is our island.
却无奈地死去
And died.
Jin
Jin!
108天之后
And after 108 days...
我是815航班的幸存者之一
I'm one of the survivors of flight 815.
六个人获救了
Six people found rescue.
女士们  先生们
Ladies and gentlemen,
大洋号的六位幸存者
the Oceanic six.
但是小岛
But the island...
消失了
vanished...
他们的朋友被留在了岛上
Sending the friends left behind...
有人吗  到底是怎么回事
Anyone?! What the hell's going on?
时光闪回
Flashing through time.
我们可能在过去  也可能到了未来
We're either in the past or we're in the future.
三年过去了
Three years passed,
那些回家的人...
and those who came home...
我们犯了一个错误
We made a mistake.
受到了召唤
Were beckoned...
我不明白
I don't understand.
它想让我们回去
It wants us to come back.
要回归小岛
To return...
Ajira航空公司316号航班
Ajira airways flight 316.
去完成未竟的事
to undo their past...
有一个办法可以让你回到过去
There's a way for you to take it all back.
你以为你可以来这为所欲为吗
You think you can come here and do whatever the hell you want?
去改变他们的命运
To alter their fate...
我要去引爆氢弹
I'm gonna detonate a hydrogen bomb.
救命
Help!
-我爱你  James  -不
- I love you, James.  - No!
他们的命运
Their destiny.
你要跟我一起来吗
Are you with me on this?
迷失
最终季
这是他们在岛上的第一夜
It was their first night on the island.
你是第一次坠机吗
First plane crash?
你怎么看出来的
What gave it away?
新手逃不过我的眼睛
I can always spot the newbies.
大洋815号的幸存者们...
and the survivors of Oceanic 815...
你觉得他们现在会来救我们吗
You'd think they would've come by now.
心存着一线被救的希望
Clung to hope for rescue.
我不知道你的名字
I don't know your name.
-我是Kate  -Jack
- I'm Kate.  - Jack.
给病人做血气分析和颈椎检查
Get me a blood gas and a c-spine.
把她送到重症监护室  把她固定好
Get her up to LCU and keep her immobilized.
Jack Shephard是一名脊椎外科医生
Jack Shephard was a spinal surgeon...
我会治好你的
I'm gonna fix you.
他被工作压得喘不过气
Consumed by his work.
我用了所有办法  我就要成功了
I got it all. I mean, I had it!
他的心脏放弃了  这不是任何人的错
His heart gave out. It's nobody's fault.
Jack同时还被一种强烈的愿望所驱使
Jack was also driven by a relentless urge
他要向他的父亲Christian证明自己
to prove himself to his father, Christian.
你在胡说些什么
What are you talking about?
我是说如果你把液囊缝上
I'm talking about you stitching up the sacs
这姑娘下半辈子就不至于瘫痪
so this girl isn't paralyzed for the rest of her life.
但是Jack从未得到机会
But Jack would never get that opportunity
因为它的父亲在悉尼去世了
because his father died in Sydney...
就是他
that's him.
Jack要把他的遗体运送回国
And it was up to Jack to bring the body home.
在岛上  大洋号的幸存者们
On the island, the Oceanic survivors
把Jack视为他们的领袖
looked to Jack as their leader.
如果我们不住在一起
If we can't live together,
就会孤独地死去
we're gonna die alone.
你做得很好
You did a good thing,
照顾每个人
taking care of everybody
让他们活着有盼头
and just giving them something to count on.
嘿  姑娘
Ah, hey, girl.
Kate Austen在爱荷华州长大
Kate Austen grew up in Iowa
她的妈妈嫁给了一个虐待狂
where her mother was married to an abusive man.
你真漂亮
You are beautiful.
有一天晚上  Kate终于忍无可忍
Then one night, Kate had enough.
Katherine  你做了什么
Katherine, what did you do?
是我在照顾你  妈妈
I took care of you, ma.
她成了一个逃犯  在逃多年...
She became a fugitive, on the run for years...
你好  Kate
hey, Kate.
终于她在澳大利亚被捕
Until she was apprehended in Australia.
大洋815号在岛上坠毁后
But when Oceanic 815 crashed on the island,
Kate找到了一个可以重新开始的地方
Kate found a place to begin anew.
我想告诉你我以前做过什么
I wanna tell you what I did.
这不重要  Kate
It doesn't matter, Kate.
我们都应该重新开始
We should all be able to start over.
在岛上
On the island,
Kate发现自己
Kate found herself
被两个截然不同的男人所吸引
drawn to two different men...
Jack  受人尊敬的领袖
Jack, the honorable leader
还有Sawyer  魅力十足的流氓
and Sawyer, the charming rogue.
你跟医生说过咱俩的事了吗
Did you tell the doc about you and me?
没有  但他知道
No, but he knows.
既然那已经不是问题
Well, now if that's out of the way,
我们何不午后逍遥一下
how about a little afternoon delight?
雀斑女  等等
Freckles, wait!
想让我给你灌一张混合唱片吗
You need me to make you a mix tape?
好啊  为什么不试试
Yeah, why don't you do that.
听妈妈说
Listen to mommy.
当James Ford还是个小男孩的时候
James Ford was just a young boy
他父亲被一个叫Sawyer的人骗光了钱
when his father was swindled by a man named Sawyer.
躲到床底下  别出声
Get under the bed. Don't make a sound.
把门打开
Open this door!
James的父亲盛怒之下杀了自己的妻子
James' father went into a rage and killed his wife...
快住手  你在做什么  你到底...
Stop it! What are you doing?! What the hell are you...
然后他自杀了
just before he killed himself.
James长大后成了一个骗子
James grew up to become a con man,
他用的正是那个骗子的名字
taking the name of the man who had conned his father,
为了报仇  他来到了澳大利亚
and his need for vengeance brought him to Australia,
他以为自己找到了那个他要找的人
where he believed he'd found the man he sought.
Sawyer
Sawyer.
但他错了
But he was wrong.
你不知道自己在做什么  对吗
You don't know what you're doin', do you?
在岛上  Sawyer经常和Jack发生争执
On the island, Sawyer often clashed with Jack.
你没有认清局势  医生
You're just not looking at the big picture, doc.
你还在活在文明世界里
You're still back in civilization.
那你在哪
And where are you?
我在荒岛上
I'm in the wild.
他总是惹是生非
And he had trouble getting along.
别打了
Break it up!
住手  我们发现了一个无线电收发机
Stop! We found a transceiver
但它坏了
but it's not working.
有人能帮上忙吗  是的
Can anybody help? Yes.
不要相信这个家伙
Let's trust this guy!
我们现在是一根绳上的蚂蚱  哥们
We're all in this together, man.
我们应该尊重彼此  平等相待
Let's treat each other with a little respect.
闭嘴  猪头
Shut up, lard-o.
老烟鬼
Chain-smokin' jackass.
有些人就是那副德性
Some people have problems.
你怎么知道如何修那个东西
How do you know how to do all that?
我以前做过部队的通讯官
I was a military communications officer.
哪个部队的  空军  陆军
What were you, air force? Army?
共和国卫队
The republican guard.
是  长官
Yes, sir.
815航班坠毁以前
Before the 815 crashed,
Sayid是一名伊拉克的拷问官
Sayid was a torturer in Iraq.
有一套新设备可以供你使用
I guess you have a new skill set you can use.
但他背叛了军队
But he was conflicted,
他爱上了一个由他拷问的女人
and he fell in love with a woman he tortured.
这不是一场游戏  Nadia
This isn't a game, Nadia.
但你一直不愿退出  Sayid
And yet you keep playing it, Sayid.
守卫
Guard!
Sayid冒着生命危险让Nadia得到自由
Sayid risked his life to give Nadia her freedom...
拿着
Take it.
接着他开始全力寻找Nadia
Then spent his life searching for her.
我们知道她在哪
We know where she is.
他和中情局合作捣毁一场恐怖活动后
When he cooperated with the CIA to overthrow a terrorist plot,
以为自己终于可以回到Nadia身边
he thought he'd finally found a way back to Nadia.
但是大洋815号在岛上坠毁
But Oceanic 815 crashed on the island...
有人看到了吗
Did anybody see that?
他们面临着小岛给出的重重挑战
And that presented its own set of challenges...
好极了
Terrific.
因为这不是一个普通的岛
For this was not an ordinary island...
Jack
Jack!
这可不是想入非非
Not by any stretch of the imagination.
爸爸
Dad?
这群人远离家乡
And this group was a very long way from home.
我们收到一格信号了
Hey! We've got a bar!
是法语  搜救队  肯定是的
That's French! The rescue party... it has to be.
这是求救信号
It's a distress call.
它被一遍又一遍地播放了16年
It's been playing over and over for 16 years.
伙计们
Guys...
我们在哪
Where are we?
我知道食物很短缺
I know food's scarce...
但你的衬衫
But your shirt?
如果你找到了一个自助洗衣店  请告诉我
When you find the laundromat, let me know.
对Hugo Reyes来说
For Hugo Reyes,
坠机给他带来了特殊的心理包袱
crashing on the island carried its own special burden.
我觉得飞机失事有可能是我的错
I think the plane crash might've been my fault.
别犯傻了  你怎么可能...
Don't be daft. How could you possibly...
之前无论我去哪
hey, a lot of bad stuff used to happen
总有坏事在我周围发生
whenever I was around.
今晚的百万大乐透
that makes tonight's
累计奖金达到...
mega lotto jackpot drawing...
Hugo买了彩票  而且中了几百万
Hugo played the lottery and won millions...
4  8  15  16  23  42
4, 8, 15, 16, 23, 42.
但霉运接踵而至
but misfortune followed.
我最近也遇到一些坏事
I've had some bad luck, too.
Tito爷爷得心脏病死了
Grandpa Tito died of a heart attack,
我给妈妈买的第一座房子被烧毁了
and the first house I bought my mom burnt down.
当他的炸鸡连锁店被一颗流星摧毁时
And when his chicken franchise was destroyed by a meteor...
他终于相信自己中奖是个诅咒
he became convinced his winnings were a curse.
欢迎光临
Welcome.
坠机后  Hugo想要尽力寻找
After the crash , Hugo tried to find
小岛的光明面
the brighter side of the island.
伙计  听着  如果我们真被困在这
Dudes, listen, if we're stuck here,
光想着怎么活下来是不够的
then just surviving's not gonna cut it.
我们需要放松一下  知道吗
We need some kind of relief, you know?
我们要尽情享受生活  找点乐子
We need some way that we can, you know, have fun.
小岛对所有幸存者都产生了影响
The island had a hold on all of the survivors...
有一个人决定揭开它最深处的秘密
but one man was determined to uncover its deepest mystery.
这...   太尴尬了
well... this is... awkward.
John Locke去和他的亲生父亲碰面
John Locke met his biological father
但万万没想到自己竟然被利用了
only to learn that he was being used.
你偷了我的肾
You stole my kidney? You
你需要一个父亲  而我需要一个肾
needed a father figure, and I needed a kidney.
忘了这件事吧
Get over it.
Locke去和他的父亲对质
When Locke confronted his father,
结果却以悲剧收场
it ended in tragedy.
他重重地摔到地上  下肢瘫痪
He was left shattered and paralyzed,
但他最终启程前往澳大利亚
but he eventually made his way to Australia
为的是一个征服澳洲内陆的梦想
with a dream of conquering the outback.
请马上把我送上巴士  我能行
Just put me on the bus right now. I can do this.
不  你不行
No, you can't.
你不知道你在跟谁打交道
You don't know who you're dealing with!
永远别跟我说我不行  永远
Don't ever tell me what I can't do, ever!
当大洋815号在岛上坠落后
When Oceanic 815 crashed on the island,
John Locke从废墟中站了起来
John Locke rose from the wreckage
他发现自己竟然又能走路了
and discovered he could walk again.
这让他相信
This gave him faith
他们来岛上都是有原因的
that they were on the island for a purpose.
你觉得我们在这个地方坠机是偶然的吗
You think we crashed on this place by coincidence?
我们每个人被带到这都是有原因的
Each one of us was brought here for a reason.
是谁把我们带到这的  John
And who brought us here, John?
这个岛
The island.
但幸存者们
But the survivors
并不是第一批被带到岛上的人
were not the first people drawn to the island.
达摩组织的一组科学家
Teams of scientists from the Dharma initiative
在70年代来到这个岛上
came to the island in the 1970s.
为了研究这个岛的特殊之处
They built research stations in an attempt to understand
他们建立了研究站
the island's special properties.
独一无二的电磁波动
Unique electromagnetic fluctuations.
有一个研究站叫天鹅站
One station was called 'The Swan'
在那里一个叫Desmond的人数年来
Where a man named Desmond spent years
一直通过向电脑输入密码
entering a code into a computer
使海湾保持超高的电磁能
to keep a massive amount of electromagnetic energy at Bay.
系统崩溃  系统崩溃
System failure. System failure.
一天  Desmond忘了输密码
One day, Desmond neglected to enter the code
导致大洋815航班在岛上坠落
and caused Oceanic flight 815 to crash on the island.
岛上的原住民们
The island's original inhabitants
并不欢迎访客的到来
were not pleased to have visitors.
Goodwin  一小时内跑到那个海滩去
Goodwin, if you run you can make that shore in an hour.
Ethan  到飞机残骸那儿
Ethan, get up there to that fuselage.
可能还有幸存者  快去
There may actually be survivors. Go!
这不是你的岛
This is not your island.
这是我们的岛
This is our island.
幸存者们马上就要遇到
The Oceanic survivors would soon meet
岛上的原住民了
the island's original inhabitants.
幸存者们把这些人叫做  其他人
They would call these people the others.
你好  Jack
Hello, Jack.
他们的首领叫Benjamin Linus
There leader was a man named Benjamin Linus,
为了保护这个岛  他无所不用其极
and he would do anything in his power to protect the island.
如果有什么傻冒敢挡你的路  杀了他们
If any of them are stupid enough to get in your way, kill 'em.
嘿  欢迎你们来这个岛
Hey, welcome to the island, man.
Ben Linus来的时候是个小男孩
Ben Linus came to the island as a young boy
他的父亲参加了达摩组织
when his father joined the Dharma initiative.
但是他们过得并不愉快
But it was not a pleasant experience.
我在这个岛上被你缠得烦死了
I'm stuck here on this island... with you.
有一天  Ben遇到了那些人
Then one day, Ben met the others.
带我一起走
Take me with you.
你必须非常的耐心
You're gonna have to be very patient.
于是Ben蛰伏起来
So Ben waited,
直到他成长到青年
and when he became a young man...
再见  老爸
Good-bye, dad.
他不择手段的
He did whatever it took
帮助那些人保护这个岛远离外来的人
to help the others protect the island from outsiders
比如达摩组织
like the Dharma initiative.
你需要我们替他收尸吗
You want us to go get his body?
不用  就把他扔那儿
No. Leave him out there.
Ben加入了那些人并且当上了首领
Ben joined the others and rose to power as their leader.
他养有一个女儿
He raised a daughter
他是这个岛屿尽忠尽责的仆人
and was a devoted servant to the island.
John Loche的到来
But when John Locke arrived
让Ben觉得受到了威胁
Ben felt threatened
因为Loche对这个岛有特殊的情结
by Locke's special communion with the island.
你才呆了80天而我已经过了一整辈子
You've been here 80 days, John. I've been here my entire life.
你怎么可能比我更了解这个岛
So how is it that you think you know this island better than I do?
但并非所有那些人都视Locke为威胁
Though not all of the others regarded Locke as a threat.
有传言说
When word had gotten back here
飞机上有个脊柱骨折的人
that there was man with a broken spine on the plane
又能走路了
who could suddenly walk again...
对此我们觉得非常兴奋
Well, people here began to get very excited.
Locke加入了那些人
Locke joined the others
并且大有成为新首领之势
and would soon become their new leader.
有一个人不惜一切想要离开
But one of them wanted desperately to leave.
我想回家
I wanna go home.
这违反约定
That's not our agreement.
在你完成工作之前必须呆在这
You need to stay here until your work is finished.
我们到了
We're here.
Juliet是一个生育专家
Juliet was a fertility specialist.
那些人雇她查明
She was recruited by the others to find out
为什么这个岛上的女人都无法生育
why women on the island could not have children.
我觉得问题出在受孕阶段
I think it happens at conception.
对此我无能为力  至少在这儿是这样
There's nothing I can do about it... at least not here.
由于希望渺茫
The situation appeared hopeless,
Juliet转投到大洋航班幸存者这边
so Juliet joined the Oceanic survivors
希望能等到回家的机会
in hopes of finding a way home.
我想了解一下你的研究
I want to know about your research.
孕妇们都怎么了
What happens to pregnant women?
都死了
They all die.
Sun和Jin来自韩国
Sun and Jin were from Korea...
尽管他们门不当户不对
and despite their very different backgrounds,
他们还是相爱了
they fell in love.
他们的婚礼欢乐喜庆
Their wedding was joyful,
但他们的婚姻很快陷入了黑暗
but their marriage soon darkened,
Sun谋划着在悉尼的时候离开Jin
and Sun planned an escape from Jin when the two were in Sydney.
岛上的共同生活却再次把他们连在了一起
Life on the island brought them closer...
你怀孕了
You're pregnant.
他们再度相爱
And they fell in love once again.
但Sun的怀孕使她身陷危机
But Sun's pregnancy put her in danger.
你的妻子病得很厉害
Your wife is very sick.
如果她不离开这个岛  她会死的
If she doesn't get off this island, she will die.
这时  救援的希望重新到来
But there was new hope for rescue.
在岛上过了近90天以后
After nearly 90 days on the island,
一艘货轮航班抵达海岸不远处
a freighter arrived off the coast.
Jack把大家带到一个信号塔处
So Jack led his group to a radio tower
打电话求救
to make a call for help.
我是大洋815航班的幸存者
I'm one of the survivors of Oceanic flight 815.
你能确定我们的位置吗
Can you get a fix on our location?
当然  我们可以
Hell, yeah, we can.
他们确信  他们终于可以回家了
They believed they'd finally found a way home.
一组来自货轮上的人乘直升机来到岛上
A group from the freighter arrived by helicopter.
我是Daniel Faraday
I'm Daniel Faraday.
我来这儿实施救援
I'm here to rescue you.
他在说什么  他说的有一半我听不懂
What's his story? Half the stuff he says goes way over my head.
另一半我下辈子都听不懂
The other half goes way, way over.
Daniel Faraday是一个物理学家
Daniel Faraday was a physicist
他毕生都在研究时间旅行
who devoted his life to the study of time travel.
他带着一个科研队伍来到这个岛上
He came to the island with a science team
以及他们的飞行员  Frank Lapidus
and their pilot Frank Lapidus.
但是救援大洋航班幸存者
But rescuing the Oceanic survivors
并不是既定任务的一部分
was not the primary mission.
是Charles Widmore
This is Charles Widmore,
他的船停在岸边
the man whose boat is parked offshore.
他想怎么样
What does he want?
他想开发这个岛
Charles Widmore wants to exploit this island,
为了霸占这个岛他会不择手段
and he'll do everything in his power to possess it.
Charles Widmore有钱有势
Charles Widmore was a wealthy and powerful man
曾经是那些人的首领
who at one time was the leader of the others.
我们还会再见面的  孩子
I'll be seeing you, boy.
他被驱逐出岛  他发誓会向Ben复仇
He was banished from the island and swore vengeance on Ben.
Widmore的货轮还运载了
Widmore's freighter also carried
一支雇佣兵部队  受命俘虏Ben
a team of mercenaries with orders to capture Ben.
立刻给我滚出来
Get your ass out here right now.
我不会出这个房间
I'm not coming out of this house.
在对峙中
And in the process...
Ben的女儿Alex被杀害
Ben's daughter Alex was murdered.
你们要杀了她吗  动手啊
If you wanna kill her, go ahead and do it.
幸存者和那些人达成一项协议
So the survivors and the others made a deal...
联合起来最终打败了雇佣兵
and joined forces to defeat the mercenaries.
直升机是你的  你可以安安全全的回去
The helicopter is yours. You have a safe journey back.
那我们可以离开这个岛了
So we can go off the island?
是这个意思吗
That's it?
是这个意思
That's it.
他说什么惹你生气的话了吗  雀斑女
He say something to tick you off, Freckles?
Widmore和他的雇佣兵被打败了
With Widmore's mercenaries defeated,
这些幸存者迫不及待的想离开孤岛
the survivors were eager to leave the island.
但John Locke选择留下
But John Locke chose to stay
他向Jack提出一项请求
and had one request for Jack.
你不能说这个岛的事情
You have to lie about everything.
只有这样才能保护这个岛
It's the only way to protect it.
这只不过是个小岛罢了  John
It's an island, John.
这不是一个岛  而是奇迹发生之地
It's not an island. It's a place where miracles happen.
咱们走Freckles
Let's go, Freckles.
我早受够这鬼地方了
I've seen enough of this rock.
Jack带一些人坐直升机飞往货轮
Jack led a group to the freighter by chopper
科研小组带另一些人划小船过去
as the science team shuttled others by boat.
但是直升机一直在漏油
But the chopper was leaking fuel.
如果能减轻一百多磅
I'd feel a hell of a lot better
就好对付多了
if we were a few hundred pounds lighter.
于是Sawyer果断采取了措施
So Sawyer acted quickly...
Sawyer
Sawyer.
当他往回游的时候
And as he made his way back to the island...
在那儿  船  我看到了
There it is! The boat... I see it!
直升机接近了货轮
The chopper reached the freighter,
却发现货轮装满了炸药
only to find it was rigged with explosives.
是Jin  调头
It's Jin! Turn around!
不能调头
We can't do it.
Jin
Jin!
Sawyer游回了小岛
Sawyer reached the island...
你在这儿干什么
What are you doing here?
还以为他的朋友们已经安全了
Believing his friends were safe.
那是咱们的船吗
Is that our boat?
同时  Locke成了那些人的新首领
Meanwhile, Locke began his new role as leader of the others...
欢迎回家
Welcome home.
Ben下降到兰花站下面深处的一个洞穴
And Ben descended to a cavern deep below the Orchid station
要移动这个小岛
to move the island
以确保Charles Widmore
and ensure that Charles Widmore
再也不会找到这里
would never find it again.
但是移动岛屿的行为
But the act of moving the island
却产生了无比严重的副作用
created a profound side effect.
有人吗
Anyone?!
货轮哪去了
Where's the freighter?
刚才船还在冒着黑烟
A minute ago, that boat was coughing black smoke.
现在就什么也没了
Now there's just nothin'?
幸存者和货轮上的科学家们
The Oceanic survivors and the freighter scientists
被带向了一条非同寻常的旅程
were taken on an extraordinary journey.
Ben Linus在兰花站下面的行为
Whatever Ben Linus did down at the Orchid station
把我们赶出去了
dislodged us.
时间
Time.
他们时光穿梭岛上的无数个时代
They flashed through numerous time periods on the island.
- 现在是哪一年 - 1954年
-What year is it right now? -It's 1954.
在一次时光穿梭中
During one flash...
Jin
Jin?
他们与Jin重聚  他又活了
They reunited with Jin, who was very much alive.
但时光穿梭
But the flashes...
Charlotte
Charlotte!
却在逐渐消磨他们的生命
Were slowly killing them.
Locke认为他可以拯救留在岛上的人
Locke believed he knew how to save everyone left behind.
他们走了  所以才会这样
This is all happening because they left.
我们必须回兰花站
We have to go back to the Orchid.
你说什么
Excuse me?
那里是不幸的开始
That's where all this started.
也许也是一切的结束
Maybe it's where it'll all stop.
你好John  剩下的事情我来帮你
Hello, John. I'm here to help you the rest of the way.
Locke转动了Ben转过的轮子
Locke turned the same wheel Ben turned...
向我儿子问好
Say hello to my son.
时光穿梭停止了
and the flashes stopped.
我看结束了  我想John做到了
I think it's over. I think John did it.
现在干什么  现在我们等他回来
Now what? Now we wait for him to come back.
John Locke转动轮子以后
After John Locke turned the wheel,
Sawyer和Juliet滞留在了1974年
Sawyer and Juliet were left stranded in 1974.
他们俩  Jin和Miles
Along with Jin and Miles, they joined
加入了岛上的达摩组织
the Dharma initiative on the island
并且很快成为了那个组织的死忠
and soon became fixtures in the community.
- 嘿  头儿  - 晚上好  Enos
-Hey, Boss. -Evening, Enos.
Sawyer被任命为安防长官
Sawyer was named head of security,
Juliet成了技工
Juliet became a mechanic...
闻起来不错哦
Somethin' smells good.
他们两人在岛上共同生活
And the two made a life together on the island.
- 我爱你  - 我也爱你
-I love you. -I love you, too.
John Locke转动轮子的时候
When John Locke turned the wheel,
他被传送到突尼斯沙漠
he was transported to the Tunisian desert...
未来的第三年  2007
Three years in the future, to 2007.
他得到了Charles Widmore的帮助
He soon received help from Charles Widmore.
你那些留在岛上的朋友们
All your friends who left the island?
他们都已经回去了三年了
They've been back three years.
他们重新过上了正常的生活
They've gone back to their normal lives.
我必须把他们带回去
I have to bring them back.
我会尽己所能帮你这个忙
And I'm gonna do everything in my power to help you do that.
于是Locke动身
So Locke set out
去说服他的朋友们回到那个岛上
to convince his friends to come back to the island.
我不会回去的
I'm not going back.
答案是不
The answer is no.
不  我哪也不去
No, I'm not going anywhere with you.
我只需要说服一个人
I only need to convince one,
其他的人就会一起来了
and if I can do that, the rest will come.
Locke的任务是艰巨的
Locke's task was difficult,
但此时这项任务已经变成了危险的
but it was about to become dangerous.
Locke的不幸再度给了他一个机会
Locke's misfortune gave him one more chance.
你想干什么
What are you doing here?
我们必须回去
We have to go back.
因为是我们的命运
Because it's our destiny?
你要把这句话重复多少遍
How many times are you gonna say that to me?
再见  John
Good-bye, John.
你的父亲向你问好
Your father says hello.
什么
What?
他说他的名字叫Christian
He said his name was Christian.
他三年前就在澳大利亚死了
He died in Australia three years ago.
我把他放进棺材里的  他死了
I put him in the coffin! He's dead.
你离我远点
You leave me alone,
离其他人也远点
and you leave the rest of 'em alone!
Locke觉得他失败了
Locke believed he had failed,
正当他绝望的时候
but in his despair...
别这样
Come on.
Ben Linus找到了回岛的机会
Ben Linus found an opportunity to get back to the island
他可以继续当从前的他
and assume his old role.
我知道去哪里
I know where we go.
在洛杉矶有个女的
There's a woman here in Los Angeles.
叫Eloise Hawking
Eloise Hawking.
Eloise Hawking  你确定
Eloise Hawking? You sure?
怎么了  你认识她
Yeah. Why? You know her?
是的  John  我认识她
Yes, John. I know her.
我会想你的  John
I'll miss you, John.
真的会
I really will.
Widmore的货船沉没的时候
When Widmore's freighter was destroyed,
直升机上的人只有一个去处
the passengers on the chopper had only one place to go.
Lapidus
Lapidus!
把我们带回岛上
Fly us back to the island!
他们飞回去的时候
They made their way back
正好看到小岛
just in time to see the island...
消失了
vanish.
-小岛去哪了  -小岛不见了
- Where the hell's the island? - It's gone.
完了  伙计们  直升机没燃料了
That's it, people! We're out of fuel!
-他们生还了  -前面有条船
- They survived the crash... - There's a boat.
在茫茫大洋里获救了
And found rescue in the middle of the ocean.
在船上
And on board the search boat,
Jack和Kate
Jack and Kate
计划好了下一步该做什么
planned the next move.
Aaron我们要怎么办
What are we gonna do about Aaron?
我不知道
I don't know.
你对他真好
You're so good with him.
我万万没想到的是
The last thing I ever thought
我是个好母亲
I'd be good at is being a mum.
你知道  你以后也应该试试
You know, you should try it sometime.
飞机失事的时候
Claire was 8 months pregnant
Claire已经怀孕8个月了
at the time of the crash,
她是去洛杉矶找领养她孩子的人
and on her way to LA to give her baby up for adoption.
是个男孩
You have a little boy.
她在岛上生下了Aaron
She gave birth to Aaron on the island...
而且对Charlie产生了好感
and soon became close with Charlie.
我不想让你担心
I didn't want you to worry.
我不会有事的  Claire
I'll be fine, Claire.
但是Charlie
But Charlie drowned
帮大家寻求救援的时候淹死了
trying to help his friends find rescue.
不久之后  Claire也失踪了
And not long after, Claire went missing...
半夜的时候她突然走了
She just walked off in the middle of the night.
Kate只能帮着照顾Aaron
Leaving Kate to care for Aaron.
我觉得我们该对外说Aaron是我生的
I think we should say he's mine.
我们已经失去了很多人
After everyone we've lost,
我不想再失去他
I can't lose him, too.
Kate  要是我们想
Kate, if we're gonna protect
保护岛上的其他人
the people that we left behind,
明天早上
tomorrow morning,
我要说服大家说谎
I'm gonna have to convince everyone to lie.
你会支持我吗
Are you with me?
我一直都支持你
I have always been with you.
之后他们回到了家
And so they returned home.
Jack  Kate  Hugo  Sayid  Sun和Aaron
Jack, Kate, Hugo, Sayid, Sun and Aaron
他们被称作大洋六人组
would come to be known as the Oceanic six,
为了保护岛上的朋友
and to protect their friends left behind,
他们扭曲了坠机之后发生的事
they lied about their entire experience.
有没有可能
Is it possible
岛上还有其他幸存者
there are any other survivors from the crash
-还没被发现  -这不可能
- yet to be discovered? - Absolutely not.
大洋六人组试着回到正常的生活中
The Oceanic six tried to adjust to a normal life,
三年过去了
but three years passed,
他们还是无法忘记
and the memories of their friends left behind
岛上的朋友
continued to haunt them.
Jack
Jack.
Jack看到了他死去的父亲
Jack began seeing visions of his dead father
他经常坐跨洋航班
and took flights over the pacific,
希望有一天飞机会坠毁到岛上
hoping the plane would crash on the island.
我能再来一杯吗
Can I get another one of those,please?
还是来份报纸吧
How about a newspaper instead?
当他看到了Locke的死讯
When he read the news of Locke's death,
他震惊了
he was devastated.
但Jack最绝望的是
But in Jack's greatest despair,
他居然和Ben成为了伙伴
he formed a most unlikely alliance.
你好  Jack
Hello, Jack.
他告诉我离开小岛了吗
Did he tell you that I was off the island?
他告诉我我离岛之后
He told me that after I left the island,
发生了一些不好的事情
some very bad things happened.
他叫我回去
And he said that I had to come back.
你们都要回去
All of you have to go back.
我们也要带上他
We're gonna have to bring him, too.
这是哪里
What is this place?
达摩组织叫它灯塔站
The Dharma initiative called it the lamp post.
Jack和Ben见了Eloise Hawking
Jack and Ben met with Eloise Hawking,
她从前是The Others的头
who was once the leader of the others
也只有她才知道
and the only person who knew
怎么回到小岛
how to get back to the island.
有一架商务航班从洛杉矶飞到关岛
There's a commercial airliner flying from LA to Guam.
Ajira航空3-1-6航班
Ajira airways, flight 3-1-6.
-就是这样  -不仅如此  Jack
- So that's it? - No, that's not all, Jack.
Eloise说
Eloise explained
Jack还要把
that Jack would need to  bring the body
John Locke的尸体带上飞机
of John Locke on the plane.
John代替了之前你父亲的尸体
John is going to be a substitute of your father's.
你肯定笑翻了吧
You must be laughing your ass off,
这比你之前更疯狂
because this is even crazier than you are.
安息吧
Rest in peace.
Kate不想回小岛
Kate had no intention of going back to the island.
Aaron  Aaron
Aaron? Aaron?
但当Aaron差点走丢的时候
But when she nearly lost Aaron...
宝贝  她是你妈妈吗
Honey, is this your mommy?
她开始怀疑自己适不适合当他妈妈
She began to doubt her decision to be his mother.
Littleton女士  我是Kate Austen
Mrs. Littleton, I'm Kate Austen.
所以Kate去找了Claire的母亲
So Kate went to Claire's mother,
她还不知道Claire还活着
who had no idea that Claire was still alive.
我告诉他你是他外婆
I told him that you're his grandmother...
我不在的时候你会照顾他
that you'll take care of him while I'm gone.
你去哪里
Where are you going?
我回去找你的女儿
I'm going back to find your daughter.
欢迎搭乘Ajira航空
Welcome to Ajira air.
谢谢
Thank you, sir.
回家了的人又重聚了
And so those who came home were together once again,
每个人回岛的目的都不一样
each returning to the island for very different reasons.
很搞怪  不是吗
It's pretty crazy, huh?
我是机长Frank J. Lapidus
This is your captain, Frank J. Lapidus.
-欢迎登机  -你好  医生
- Welcome aboard. - Well, hello, doc.
Frank你在这干嘛
What are you doing here, Frank?
我一直飞这条路线
Well, I fly this route all the time.
有时候我也会飞新德里
Sometimes I take the big birds into new... Delhi.
那是Sayid还有Hurley吗
Is that Sayid? And Hurley.
等等  我们不是去关岛  是吗
Wait a second. We're not going to Guam, are we?
在大洋上航行
High over the pacific...
一种熟悉的感觉席卷了那趟航班
a familiar feeling swept through the plane.
老兄  你最好系好安全带
Dude, you might want to fasten your seat belt.
我控制住了
I have the controls.
啊  啊
Aah! Aah!
那能当跑道吗
Is that a runway?
大量仪器故障  飞机要降落了
Massive instrument failure! We're putting her down!
求救  求救  求救
Mayday! Mayday! Mayday!
我们是Ajira航空3-1-6号
This is Ajira 3-1-6.
紧抱防碰撞
Brace for impact.
嘿
Hey.
大洋六人组回到了岛上
The Oceanic six were back on the island...
Frank  Sun
Frank? Sun.
他们回到了两个不同的时间里
Separated by two very different time periods.
老天  发生了什么
Oh, my God. What happened?!
Sun跟着飞机一起回到了2007年
Sun landed with the plane in 2007...
-他们去哪里了 -他们不见了
- Where'd they go? - They're gone.
-去哪了  -我怎么知道
- Gone where? - How would I know?
其他人发现他们
But her friends found themselves
回到了岛上的  30年前
back on the island... 30 years earlier.
Jin
Jin?
老兄  我真不敢相信
Dude, I can't believe it.
哦
Oh!
一下就能抱起来  金刚
Easy on the ribs there, Kong.
真怀念你叫我绰号
I actually missed that.
我也想你了  Hugo
I missed you, too, Hugo.
Sawyer
Sawyer.
医生
Doc.
Kate见到你真高兴
Good to see you, Kate.
我也是James
You too, James.
你们穿着达摩的旧制服干嘛
So what's up with you guys and the old Dharma jumpsuits?
我们是达摩的一员
We're in the Dharma initiative.
现在是1977年
It's 1977.
什么
Uh... what?
飞机上的其他人呢
What about everyone else from the plane?
他们可能还在那里
They could still be out there.
其他人你指谁
What do you mean, everyone else?
Sayid也在飞机上
Sayid was on the plane, too,
还有Lapidus和Sun
Lapidus and Sun.
Jin去找Sun的时候
As Jin began his search to find Sun,
Sawyer为他们想到了掩饰身份的方法
Sawyer created a cover story for the new arrivals,
你们是第二波招募来的
y'all are gonna be the second batch of recruits
乘潜水艇来的
comin' in off the sub,
现在就去码头
pullin' into port right about now.
大家一起说  吉祥  吉祥
everybody say, "Namaste!" Namaste.
30年之后的未来
30 years in the future,
Sun开始找Jin
Sun began her search for Jin.
有人吗
Hello.
-你是谁  -我是Christian
- Who the hell are you? - My name's Christian.
我在找我丈夫
I'm looking for my husband.
真遗憾  找你丈夫还有段路要走
I'm sorry, but you have a bit of a journey ahead of you.
这从哪里来的  谁给你的
Where did you get this? Who gave this to you?
他说他叫Christian
He said his name was Christian.
他说我要是想再见到我丈夫
He said if I ever wanted to see my husband again,
就要在这等John Locke
I had to wait here for John Locke.
但他都死了  我们要捏一把汗了
But considering he's dead, we ain't holding our breath.
你最好看看窗外
Well, you might want to look outside.
一个长得像John Locke的人
A man who looked like John Locke
出现在了岛上
was on the island...
早上好
Morning.
你好
Hello.
他让你产生了很多疑问
And he raised many questions.
没人记得你在那架飞机上
Nobody remembers you being on the plane.
我也不记得我在那飞机上
Well, I don't remember being on it either.
那你记得什么
What do you remember?
我记得我奄奄一息了
I remember dying.
你好Ben
Hello, Ben.
天哪
My God.
-你还活着  -是的
- You're alive. - Yes, I am.
Ben如果你跟我们一起去我会很高兴
Ben, I'd appreciate it if you'd join us.
什么  John
What, John,
你敢相信我和我的人吗
don't you trust me here with my former people?
我不怕你做任何事情  Ben
I'm not afraid of anything you can do anymore, Ben.
Ben马上意识到
Ben quickly realized
眼前的这个人已经不同于从前的了
there was something very different about this man.
你怎么知道你要去哪里
How is it that you know where you're going?
他不再被恐惧与犹豫所困扰
He was no longer plagued by fear and doubt...
我就是知道
I just know.
他比从前更能利用
But more in touch with the power of the island
-小岛所蕴含的力量  -我带晚餐来了
- than he'd ever been before. - I brought dinner.
Richard  好久不见
Hello, Richard. It's been a while.
跟他说话的人是谁
Who's that man he's talking to?
他叫Richard Alpert
His name is Richard Alpert.
他可以算是顾问
He's a kind of... Advisor.
Richard Alpert
在岛上生活了很长一段时间
had lived on the island for a very long time,
而且他不会变老
and he did not appear to age.
他对小岛和头领绝对忠诚
He was a devoted servant to the island and its leaders.
现在我是头了  是吗
I am the leader now, right?
是的  John  没错
Yes, John, that's right.
很好  我想你带我去见Jacob
Good. Then I would like you to take me to Jacob.
-可以吗  -当然  没问题
- Can you do that? - Yeah, of course.
好极了
Fantastic.
我们都对一个人负责  John
We all answer to someone, John.
-那他是谁  -他叫Jacob
- And whom might that be? - His name is Jacob.
那个叫Jacob的男人
The man known as Jacob
对于岛上的居民来说是个迷
was a mystery to the island inhabitants.
Jacob想这么做
Jacob wanted it done.
Jacob只跟我说话  John
Jacob talks to me, John.
没有其他人见过他
No one else has ever seen him?
-是的  -这也太省事了
- That's right. - How convenient.
几个世纪以来
Jacob was a
Jacob就是这个岛的精神象征
spiritual presence on the island for centuries
他见到过很多人到这个岛上
and has seen many people make their way to his home.
我想你在这是因为那艘船
I take it you're here 'cause of the ship.
他们怎么会找到这个岛
How did they find the island?
他们到了之后你去问问
You'll have to ask 'em when they get here.
我不用问  你把他们带来的
I don't have to ask. You brought them here.
你还想证明我错了  是吗
Still trying to prove me wrong, aren't you?
你是错了
You are wrong.
是吗
Am I?
Jacob的乐观
Jacob's optimism
对于他的对手来说正好相反
was a stark contrast to his Nemesis.
他们来到这里  打斗
They come. They fight.
破坏  堕落
They destroy. They corrupt.
事实总是如此
It always ends the same.
这只发生过一次
It only ends once.
发生那些事之前的  就算是进步了
Anything that happens before that is just progress.
但他跟这个黑衣人的冲突
But the conflict with this man in black
有规则阻止他们互相伤害
had rules which prevented them from harming one another.
你知道我有多想杀了你吗
Do you have any idea how badly I want to kill you?
知道
Yes.
总有一天我会找到机会的  朋友
One of these days, I'm going to find a loophole, my friend.
那好  当你找到了  我就在这儿等你
Well, when you do, I'll be right here.
Jacob并没有把自己禁锢在小岛上
Jacob did not confine himself to the island.
抱歉  先生  你能帮我下吗
Excuse me, sir? Could you help me?
你想找什么
What are you looking for?
他和大洋生还者仍保持着联系
He made contact with some of the Oceanic survivors...
在他们生命中重要的时刻
at critical moments in their lives...
别害怕  你不会有事的
Don't worry. Everything's gonna be all right.
尽管他们根本不知道他是谁
Though they had no idea who he was.
是你的吗 我想我只是需要再努力点
one of these yours? I guess it just needed a little push.
Jacob的有些来访甚至远远早于
Some of Jacob's visits occurred long before
大洋号飞机坠毁于小岛的时间
the Oceanic passengers crashed on the island.
我对你父母的事深表遗憾  James
I'm very sorry about your mother and father, James.
听话啊  Katie
Be good, Katie.
对其他人...   抱歉
And for others... Oh. Sorry.
其实  我就在下几个街口下车
Actually, I'm only going a few blocks,
如果你愿意我们可以一起  他一直引导
if you want to share. He provided guidance
他们直到他们最终
that would eventually lead
回到小岛上  Ajira316航班
them back to the island. Ajira airways flight 316.
你自己决定  Hugo
It's your choice, Hugo.
但在小岛上  Jacob一直是个谜
But on the island, Jacob remained a mystery,
同时有个人非常渴望找到他  有段时间
and one man was very eager to find him. For some time,
你们一直听命于一个叫Jacob的人
you all have been accepting orders from a man named Jacob.
我将要去会会Jacob
Well, I'm gonna go and see Jacob,
同时我希望你们都可以和我一起去
and I'd like all of you to come with me.
我开始觉得John Lock会成为个大麻烦
I'm starting to think John Locke is gonna be trouble.
你以为我为什么想杀了他
Why do you think I tried to kill him?
我知道我们过去一直有分歧  John
I know we've had our differences in the past, John,
可如果你需要Jacob帮你和你的人重聚
but if you need Jacob to help you reunite your people,
那我愿意做任何
then I'll do whatever...
我对和我的人重聚没兴趣
I'm not interested in being reunited with my people.
那我们去见Jacob是为什么
Then why are we going to Jacob?
因为这样我就可以杀了他
So I can kill him.
可为了能杀了Jacob  这个人需要帮助
But in order to kill Jacob, this man needed help.
你为什么要我杀了Jacob  John
Why do you want me to kill Jacob, John?
因为
Because...
尽管你对这个岛如此忠心耿耿
Despite your loyal service to this island,
你却不得不亲眼看着自己女儿被枪杀
you had to watch your own daughter gunned down
可你的奖励呢  却是被驱逐出这个岛
right in front of you. And your reward? You were banished.
而你所做的一切
And you did all this
都是以一个你从未见过的人的名义
in the name of a man you've never even met.
所以这个问题应该是  Ben
So the question is, Ben,
你他妈为什么不想杀了Jacob
why the hell wouldn't you wanna kill Jacob?
但是Jacob在Ajira航班上有朋友
But Jacob had friends aboard the Ajira flight.
箱子里是什么  我们得给某人看看
What's in the box? We need to show it to somebody.
为什么  让他们知道他们在和谁对着干
What for? So they'll know who they're up against.
Ilana是Jacob的忠实追随者
Ilana was a devoted follower of Jacob...
他也出现在她的关键时刻
and he came to her at a critical time.
我在这儿因为我需要你帮助
I'm here because I need your help.
你愿帮我吗  Ilana
Will you help me, Ilana?
愿意
Yes.
但是这个长得像Locke的人
But the man who looked like Locke
最终到达了他的目的地
finally reached his destination.
你好  Jacob
Hello, Jacob.
你找到机会了
Well, you found your loophole.
确实是
Indeed I did.
而且你无法想象
And you have no idea
为了到这里
what I've gone through
我经历了些什么
to be here.
你俩以前见过吗
Have you met before?
某种意义上上来说是
In a manner of speaking.
外面
Outside...
Ilana和她的队伍到了
Ilana and her team arrived.
别开枪
Don't shoot.
Richard  我是Ilana
Richard, I'm Ilana.
我有东西给你看
I have something you need to see.
我不懂了
I don't understand.
如果这个是Locke
If this is Locke...
那里面的是谁
Who's in there?
一切都准备就绪了
All the pieces were in place...
做我叫你做的  Ben
Do what I asked you to, Ben.
留给Ben面对面...
Leaving Ben face-to-face...
Benjamin...和这个岛的精神领袖
Benjamin... With the island's spiritual leader.
不论他和你说了什么  我想你懂一件事
Whatever he's told you, I want you to understand one thing...
你一直有选择的机会
you have a choice.
但Jacob无视Ben太久了
But Jacob had neglected Ben for far too long.
终于现在  经过那么多次
Oh... so now, after all this time,
你终于决定不在无视我了
you've decided to stop ignoring me.
可惜
Well...
他们要来了
they're coming.
什么
What?
他们要来了
They're coming.
让我把这事搞清楚
Let me get this straight.
所有的这些事都已经发生了  是的
All this already happened. Yes.
那么我下一句会说什么  我不知道
Then what am I gonna say next? I don't know.
哈  那你就是谬论
Ha! Then your theory is wrong!
Hugo企图理解时空旅行
Hugo attempted to comprehend
的复杂规则
the complex laws of time travel,
同时Jack和Kate
and along with Jack and Kate,
他尽力让自己适应1970年达摩组织的
he did his best to adjust to life
生活 我们为什么不拼车
in the Dharma initiative of the 1970s. Why don't we carpool?
这可以减慢全球变暖  当然现在还没发生
It'll help with global warming, which hasn't happened yet,
所以或许我们可以阻止它
so maybe we can prevent it.
Sawyer的掩饰故事很成功
Sawyer's cover story worked,
他们各自都在社区中被分配了工作
and they were each assigned jobs within the community.
记得试试这个蘸酱
And don't forget to try the dipping sauces.
真的把火腿变的更好吃
They really bring out the ham.
但他们的到来给Juilet带来很大压力
But their arrival weighed heavily on Juliet,
她知道关于Sawyer和Kate的过去
who knew Sawyer's history with Kate
也相信她和Sawyer的生活将从此改变
and believed her life with Sawyer would never be the same.
一切都结束了  不是吗
It's over, isn't it?
什么结束了
What's over?
我们的过家家
Us... playing house.
我们在边界上抓了个人质
We got a hostile inside the perimeter.
对Sayid来说  快走
As for Sayid... Move.
他和他的朋友在
He was separated from his friends
闪光的时候失散了
at the time of the flash,
同时他的到来也引起别人对新成员
and his arrival aroused suspicion
的猜疑 我想我们找到Sayid
of the new recruits. I guess we found Sayid.
但在这岛上的所有事...谁能帮我下吗
But everything on the island... Hey, can I get a hand with this?
都即将改变  Dan
Was about to change. Dan.
是你啊  Miles
Hey, Miles.
你他妈回来干什么啊  Dan
What the hell are you doing back here, Dan?
这是我回来干的事
This is what I'm doing back here.
Daniel Faraday和大洋生还者一起忍受着
Daniel Faraday endured the time flashes on the island
时空闪回的痛苦
with the rest of the Oceanic` survivors,
在1950年间的到访让
and during a visit to the 1950s,
他知道其他人有氢弹
he learned the others had a hydrogen bomb.
你得把这个从发射台上拆下来埋了
You need to take it off this platform and bury it.
当Faraday出现在1970年时
When Faraday arrived in the 1970s,
他集中全力在找到一条
he focused his energies on finding a way
改变未来的方法
to change the future,
同时新的达摩站正在建设中
and with a new Dharma station under construction,
时机非常完美
the timing was perfect.
达摩组织的人在天鹅站
The Dharma folks at the Swan work site...
他们就要钻到地底下了
they're gonna drill into the ground
会意外接触到巨大能量
and accidentally tap into a massive pocket of energy.
为了控制它  他们不得不水泥浇灌
In order to contain it, they're gonna have to
整个区域  就像切尔诺贝利核电站
cement the entire area in, like Chernobyl.
他们将花费下个20年
they're gonna spend the next 20 years
靠按按钮控制那个地下能量
keeping that energy at bay by pressing a button...
你们的朋友Desmond  系统错误
A button that your friend Desmond... system failure.
有天将没来得及去按那按钮
Will one day fail to push,
而导致你们的飞机在这个岛上失事
and that will cause your plane to crash on this island.
我觉得我们可以改变这个
I think we can change that.
这样那个舱就永远不会被建成
Then that hatch will never be built,
你们的飞机就会像原定计划安全着陆
and your plane will land just like it's supposed to.
那你究竟打算怎么摧毁那股能量
And just how exactly do you plan on destroying this energy?
我会引爆那颗氢弹
I'm gonna detonate a hydrogen bomb.
Jack受到了鼓舞
Jack was inspired.
那个炸弹在哪里  Richard
Where's the bomb, Richard? Where is it?
当 Faraday被枪杀后
and when Faraday was shot and killed,
Jack承担了Faraday的使命
Jack assumed Faraday's mission.
我们从那飞机上消失到了这里
We disappeared off that plane and ended up here
是因为这是我们的命运
because this is our destiny.
Jack说服其他人带他找到那炸弹
Jack convinced the others to take him to the bomb.
如果他能够阻止大洋815航班坠毁
If he could prevent flight 815 from ever crashing,
他就可以消除幸存者忍受的
he could eliminate all the pain and suffering
的痛苦和煎熬
the survivors endured.
现在干什么
Well... now what?
利用Faraday的日记当做指导
Using Faraday's journal as a guide,
Sayid取出了炸弹的核心
Sayid extracted the core of the bomb.
但是去天鹅站只有一条路可走
But there was only one way to get to the Swan site...
就是穿越达摩组织的居住地
and that was through the Dharma compound...
大事不好了  不是吗
that's not good, right?
抓住Sayid和其余的新来成员
Which was already on High alert
已经是最高的警报了
to hunt down Sayid and the rest of the new arrivals.
上车
Get in.
在Jin和Hurley的帮助下  Jack和Sayid逃脱了
with Jin and Hurley's help, Jack and Sayid escaped.
我不知道我们要去哪儿  天鹅站
I don't know where we're going. The Swan site.
那是什么  Jack  天鹅站是什么
What it is. Jack, what's at the Swan?
我想我找到了让你回到你老婆身边的办法
I think I found a way to get you back to your wife.
别担心  兄弟
Don't worry, dude.
Jack改变了未来后一切都没事了
Everything'll be fine when Jack changes the future.
是时候了我该走了
It's time for me to go.
小心  它只要一受撞击就会爆炸
Be careful. It's rigged to explode on impact.
Sayid  这回一定会成功
Sayid, this is gonna work.
Jack准备好了  洛杉矶见
Jack was ready... See you in Los Angeles.
可在他可以结束一切开始的地方时  Jack
But before he could finish what he started... Jack?
他需要Kate站在他这边
He needed Kate on his side.
我一生中从来没像这次如此确信过
Nothing in my life has ever felt so right.
我只需要你相信我
I just need you to believe that.
这个关不上了
it won't shut down!
有东西把钻头往下拉  我们钻到中心了
Something's pulling the drill down. We hit the pocket!
就要发生了
It's about to happen.
这次你相信我吗
Are you with me on this?
相信
Yes.
那我们走
Then let's go.
当Jack接近了天鹅站
When Jack approached the Swan site,
达摩组织的警卫发现了他
he was spotted by Dharma security...
但是救援很快就到了
but help soon arrived.
把枪放下
Aah! Put your guns down.
好了  你可以下去了  医生
All right, you can come down out now, doc!
大多数人相信完成的事
Most believe that what's done
就已经结束了
is done.
你无论多努力
You cannot change fate,
都无法改变命运
no matter how hard you try.
而那些挑战命运之事的人
And those who challenge what is destined
总是会
will always be met
以失败告终
with disappointment...
这里可不像洛杉矶机场
this don't look like LAX
命运总会
for fate has a way...
做主它自己的进程
of charting its own course.
救命  Juilet
Aah! Help! Juliet!
Help! Juliet!
不
aah! No!
No! Aah!
不准你离开我
Don't you leave me.
没事的
it's okay.
不准你离开我  我爱你
Don't you leave me! I love you.
不  你别放手  我爱你  James
No, you don't let go. I love you, James.
不  我真的爱你
No. I love you so much.
不  不  别放手
No! No, don't let go! Aah!
Juliet!
可在人们向命运之手投降之前
But before one surrenders to the hands of destiny...
有人或许会考虑到
one might consider
人类精神的力量
the power of the human spirit...
和流淌在人自由意志里的
and the force that lies
巨大力量
in one's own free will.
快爆啊
Come on!
come on!
快啊  你这个狗娘养的
Come on, you son of a bitch!